// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " The length, expansiveness and tallness of a cuboid are in the proportion 6:5:4 and its entire surface region is 33300 cm2 . Its volume is: ",
    answer: " 405000 cm3",
    options: [
      " 45000 cm3",
      " 405000 cm3",
      " 455000 cm3",
      "information deficient"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "8 men can do a bit of work in 12 days. 4 ladies can do it in 48 days and 10 kids can do it in 24 days. In how long can 10 men, 4 ladies and 10 kids together finish the bit of work? ",
    answer: "6 days",
    options: [
      " 5 days",
      " 15 days",
      "28 days",
      "6 days"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Two no. are in the extent 3/2 :8/3, when each of these are extended by 15 , their extent gets the chance to be 5/3 :5/2 . The greater of the no. is :",
    answer: "48",
    options: [
      "27",
      "36",
      "48",
      "64"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " The sum of two numbers is 45 and difference is 1/9 of their sum. What is their L.C.M: ",
    answer: "100",
    options: [
      "100",
      "150",
      "200",
      "250"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "1/0.04 = ?",
    answer: "25",
    options: [
      " 1/40",
      " 2/5 ",
      "2.5",
      "25"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The average age of 80 girls was 20 years, the average age of 20 of them was 22 years and that of another 20 was 24 years. Find the average age of the remaining  girls. ",
    answer: "17",
    options: [
      " 17",
      " 19 ",
      "21",
      "15"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " A shopkeeper professes to sell all things at a discount of 20% ,but increases selling price of each article by 30% .His gain on each article is ",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      " 3",
      " 4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " Choose the pair of words that best completes the sentence: The -------- of the timetable caused some ---------- ",
    answer: "revision/inconvenience",
    options: [
      "  rivision/inconvenience ",
      " revision/inconvenience",
      " revission/inconvenience ",
      " revition/inconvenience  "
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "  Which of these is the missing word? kick, ______, walk     ",
    answer: "hand",
    options: [
      " throw",
      " toes",
      "shin",
      "hand"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];